Doctor,
how is he?
It's been eight hours. How is it?
The surgery wasn't successful.
Dad passed away.
My condolences, everyone.
Now, I need to announce
an official matter.
Mr. He
left a will.
I will now
formally read it.
The 60% shares
of He Group,
the He Manor,
and all real estate,
safes,
and valuables in Rongcheng
will all be inherited by Li Zhangxin.
That is all.
Dad gave me all his love.
It turns out
Dad supported us being together.
I didn't expect it.
He opposed us so much back then,
yet he gave all his property to you.
By the way, Ms. Shu.
About the huge insurance policy
you bought for your husband
and Mrs. He...
Due to your husband's accident,
it has now officially taken effect.
But
Mrs. He is currently missing.
So for now...
We will find her.
Zhang Xin,
I finally get to see your downfall.
How did you know?
His shoes were covered in mud
when he came back that day.
I knew he went to the orphanage again.
Ever since the orphanage was abandoned,
He Shi often comes back here.
He's a neat freak.
If he hadn't come here,
he wouldn't have mud
on his shoes.
Besides Zhang Xin and the butler,
why is there another skeleton?
It should be the director's.
I thought
he came back here out of nostalgia.
Now it seems
he was checking on the bodies.
He actually has three lives on his hands.
This is terrifying.
We should call the police right now.
The police have found that
the late richest man in Rongcheng,
He Shi, the eldest son of the He family,
was involved in three cases.
The police have confirmed that
the deceased are
Mrs. He, Zhang Xin,
the former butler of the He family,
Liu Dan,
and the director of an orphanage.
Mei,
all the storms have passed.
I believe the days ahead
will be beautiful
and peaceful.
Fortunately,
I'm not alone in the end.
You two,
stop being so lovey-dovey.
We're invited to a fashion gala tonight.
Let's go together.
Okay, sure.
Good evening,
Miss, Second Young Master,
and Eldest Young Mistress.